boomf.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy - Boomf

Boomf is operated by Boomf Ltd. Here at Boomf we recognise that your privacy is important. We want to help you to protect your personal information and keep it safe. We will never sell, rent or disclose any of your personal information, including your email address, to any third party without your prior or explicit consent. We may contact you to let you know about new products or offers from Boomf Ltd.

Unless you give us specific consent to act otherwise, the following privacy policy will govern how we will handle the personal information that you provide to us.

This is a legal document which sets out how we will handle your personal data and should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions which can be found at [boomf.com/terms](https://boomf.com/terms). This Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms and Conditions.

You can access this policy on any page on our website by following the link at the bottom of each page.

## What personal information do we collect?

When you visit, create an account or make a purchase with Boomf we may ask you to provide us with some, or all, of the following information:

Full name  
Email address and password  
Billing and postal address  
Payment method details (processed through Stripe)  
Your images uploaded  
Telephone number  
Instagram/Facebook name (upon approval)  

You can see the information that we hold about you by logging on to Boomf and checking your Account Details. Once images are uploaded they are stored in an image library in your account. If you have any queries please get in contact. 

## How do we use your personal information at Boomf?

Your personal data is collected, processed and stored on our internal database to:  
• Fulfil your order with Boomf.  
• Communicate with you about Boomf and other Boomf products.  
• Provide you with order and billing information.  

For legitimate business reasons we may process your data to improve the service we provide on our website. For example analysing data we hold on you to improve our customer experience, and offer you products that we believe you are likely to be interested in. 

We also use the non-personally identifiable information and certain technical information about your computer in order to operate, maintain and manage Boomf.

## Controlling your personal information

If you would like to access, amend or delete and information at any time this can be done through accessing your account with Boomf. If you have any questions please email us at [gdpr@boomf.com](mailto:gdpr@boomf.com).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, this can be amended in your account. Alternatively please email us as soon as possible, we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Payment

Payment for Boomf products is made via credit/debit card and Stripe. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

We follow the principles of the General Data Protection Regulation of May 2018: 

• We are fully aware of where your data is being held & when outside the EU, have ensured appropriate compliance is in place   
• Your personal data can be amended or removed   
• Policies are in place to ensure accountability and privacy of all personal data 

The lawful basis for processing personal data is that of Legitimate interest.

A Data Protection Officer (DPO) has not been appointed because Boomf do not meet the necessary criteria as set out by the Information Commissioners Office (ICO). 

Boomf Limited is registered with the Information Commissioner as a data controller.

## Your Rights

You have a number of rights under GDPR 2016/679 you can exercise over your data:

• The right to receive a copy of your data free of charge (know as a Subject Access Request)  
• The right to receive certain data in an electronic format that can be given to another provider (a portability request)  
• The right to have data corrected if it is inaccurate   
• The right to ask us to stop processing or object to processing under certain circumstances   
• The right to ask us to delete personal data   
• The right to withdraw consent at any time when that is the legal basis for our processing 

If you would like to exercise any of these rights please get in contact with our customer services team. If you wold like a copy of the information held on you please email [gdpr@boomf.com](mailto:gdpr@boomf.com) or write to Boomf, Unit 32, 35 Corbridge Crescent, London, E2 9EZ. 

We obtain personal data when an account is created through our website or an order is placed. On this basis, we believe there is a valid interest for contacting you for marketing purposes.

You can request to be removed from our marketing database at any time by:

• Clicking the 'unsubscribe' button on any email correspondence from us,  
• Sending through your details and request via email to hello@boomf.com,   
• Or replying to any information we have sent you.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

## How we use cookies

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and make the service easier to use for our members. We do this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends - for example, we use cookies to allow you to automatically log in to the service after the first user session.

Boomf may store up to two types of cookies on your computer:  
• A unique ID is stored in a permanent cookie so that you do not need to retype information every time you visit our site.  
• Your web browser’s session identification is stored in a temporary cookie to help prevent unauthorised use of your account.

The list below details the cookies used by Boomf:

Boomf  
Necessary cookies  
These cookies are required to enable core functionality, for example adding a product into your basket. Simply put the website can't function without them. The information collected through these cookies is only used for this purpose and is never shared or sold to third parties.  

Google Analytics  
Performance/analytics cookies  
These cookies help us to improve our website by collecting and reporting information on how the website is used. This helps us identify where you are struggling to use the website, and improve it to make the experience better for you. The data collected through this cookie is anonymous.   

Facebook, Twitter, Google Adwords, Bing, LinkedIn, Youtube, Snapchat, Adroll, Pinterest  
Advertising cookies  
These cookies track our paid advertising activity through the advertisers listed above. Each advertiser uses its own cookies, and we use the information to serve ads that are relevant to your interests and identify where are ads are effective.   

## Managing cookies

You can choose to accept, decline or specify which cookies you want to activate when visiting our website. However, be aware that some parts of the Boomf website may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Changes in our Privacy Policy.

If we make any change to this policy this page will be updated to reflect such change. If appropriate, we will notify you by email. 

If you have any questions with regards to our Privacy Policy get in contact at [hello@boomf.com](mailto:hello@boomf.com).

Privacy policy last updated 24th May 2018.

There seems to have been an error.
